http://www.animalsheltering.org/privacy

Skip to main content
The Humane Society of the United States (The HSUS) and its affiliates are committed to your right to privacy and to keeping your personal information private. You can visit our websites without telling us who you are or revealing any identifying information about yourself. However, because our websites include areas in which visitors can provide personally identifying information, we have developed this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and practices regarding information we collect about you.
This Privacy Policy governs the URL http://www.animalsheltering.org and certain electronic communications sent out by The HSUS. This web site is owned and operated by The Humane Society of the United States for the benefit of its members and other visitors interested in the protection of all animals. Our headquarters is located at 1255 23rd Street, NW Suite 450, Washington, DC 20037. The HSUS reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be preceded by a notice posted to this Privacy Policy at least ten (10) days prior to the effective date of such change.
How We Collect Information About You
Information You Voluntarily Provide
The HSUS collects and maintains certain personal information about you when you send us an e-mail or complete any of our online forms, such as when you request information from us, subscribe to one of our online newsletters, sign up for mobile text alerts, or forward a web page, electronic postcard, or electronic newsletter. Such information may include your name, mailing address, and e-mail address; it may also include a mobile phone number, the e-mail addresses of those to whom you forward HSUS electronic content, and any other information collected in the forms. You may be asked to provide credit card information to become a member of The HSUS, contribute to The HSUS, purchase certain information or materials from The HSUS, or subscribe to various HSUS publications.
Other Information
animalsheltering.org also collects certain other information that cannot identify you personally when you visit our web site. This information includes your IP address and your domain name. animalsheltering.org logs these IP addresses and domain names, and aggregates them for system administration and to monitor the use of our site. We use the aggregated information to measure the number of visits to our site, the average time spent on our site, the number of pages viewed, and various other site statistics. This monitoring helps us to provide a more useful and engaging online experience to HSUS.org visitors, and helps us to improve the quality of our content.
The HSUS uses cookies in order to make the results available for your on-site searches. Cookies are not used for any other reason on this site. A cookie is a small file that is sent out by a web site, accepted by the user's browser, and placed on the user's hard drive. You can always set your browser to warn of cookies being placed, and then chose which cookies you want to accept. The HSUS does not match any information gathered by cookies with personal information you may have voluntarily submitted to The HSUS.
The HSUS uses remarketing with Google Adwords and analytics to display content specific advertisements to visitors that have previously visited our site when those visitors go to other websites that have the Google Display Network implemented. The HSUS also uses Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.
The HSUS and other third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party and third-party cookies together to inform and serve ads based on a visitor’s past visits to our website.
You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's Ads Settings at any time. Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
Ways Information About You Is Used
We may use the information you voluntarily provided to contact you regarding animal-related issues we feel you may be interested in, to keep you updated regarding The HSUS's programs, and to extend an invitation to you to support our programs. We may also send such information to the people whose e-mail addresses you provide when forwarding HSUS electronic content. When we do so, our sole intent is to enlarge our family of informed animal advocates. Every recipient of our electronic communications can quickly and easily "opt out" of future such communications by following the instructions on any electronic communication we send.
From time to time, we may make such voluntary information, excluding credit card information and email addresses (which will never be disclosed), available to The HSUS's affiliate organizations or to sponsors or licensees that provide special programs or services we think you might find interesting or beneficial. The HSUS uses very strict standards in determining which reputable companies become sponsors and licensees, to ensure that such organizations are committed to the protection of visitors' privacy and committed to the goals of The HSUS. If your volunteered personal information will be used in any manner other than as stated above, such use shall be specifically posted. If you wish to update or remove your information, or if you do not wish your information to be shared with affiliated third parties, please e-mail us at info@animalsheltering.org. You may also unsubscribe at any time in every issue of our newsletters.
Other
From time to time, The HSUS and its affiliates may link to other web sites not affiliated with. We attempt to link only to those web sites which also respect a visitor's privacy and our animal protection goals. However, we cannot be responsible for the content or policies of third-party web sites. Please check with these third-party organizations or companies for their specific privacy policies. If you find inoperable links or are concerned about any of the sites that we currently link to, please inform us by contacting us at
info@animalsheltering.org.
Security
The HSUS uses generally accepted, industry-standard security systems, software, and encryption technologies–-Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)--for the secure transfer of personal and financial data and to protect against unauthorized access to The HSUS's servers, equipment, and other components of our online presence. This includes using industry-standard security systems to protect credit card processing information. Our web servers are stored off-site at multiple, physically secure facilities with limited access.
Contacting The HSUS or its affiliates
If you would like to contact us about correcting information we might have collected, or if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at info@animalsheltering.org or write to us at Animal Sheltering Website, The HSUS, 1255 23rd Street NW, Suite 450, Washington, DC 20037.
Advertisements
Fall 2020
In this issue: A decade of promoting shelter pets; summer camp, COVID style; innovation sensations; hole-istic cat housing; creating videos with viral potential; teaming up with sports stars to promote your organization; new approaches to feline retroviruses; and more.
Summer 2020
In this issue: The HSUS Pets for Life team shifts tactics but retains core beliefs during the COVID-19 pandemic; new science about cat allergies may prevent surrenders; an upstate New York shelter teams with local pizzerias to promote adoptable animals; VCA adds a nail in the coffin of elective declawing; an Idaho nonprofit helps ‘sweeten the pot’ for harder-to-place cats; and more.
Spring 2020
In this issue: Facial recognition may be a new way to help locate lost pets; a Baltimore shelter finds “bad” pet portraits good for fundraising; why and how organizations can enlist volunteers with disabilities; veterinarians and trap-neuter-return experts share their perspectives on feral fosters; the growing trend of shelters mentoring shelters proves a win-win for the field; a dog rebounds from horrible injuries; and more.
Animal Sheltering magazine
Fall 2020
Stepping up to the plate
Viral shift
Lights, camera, adoptions!
Learn More
Tools + Resources
Grants
State Director Lookup
Jobs
Store
Get The Scoop! email updates
Animal Sheltering's bimonthly e-newsletter delivers the latest news, training, education opportunities and special offers to help you in your work with animals. Subscribe to The Scoop! today.
